export const generalknowledgeQuestions = [
    {
      question:
        "Find the missing number in the given number pattern: 120, 145,170, ? , 220, 245",
      options: ["195", "180", "210", "205"],
      correctAnswer: "195",
    },
    {
      question: "If Toffee means Biscuit, Biscuit means Cake, Cake means Burger, then ____ is cut on birthday.",
      options: ["Toffee", "Cake", "Burger", "Biscuit"],
      correctAnswer: "Biscuit",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the difference between the place values of encircled digits in the given number : 4 (6) 3 (8) ",
      options: ["608", "592", "92", "68"],
      correctAnswer: "592",
    },
    {
      question: "9748 is same as ________",
      options: ["900+70+40+8", "9000+700+40+8", "9000+400+70+8", "8000+400+70+9"],
      correctAnswer: "9000+700+40+8",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Lalita has Rs 250. She wants to buy a handbag that costs Rs 310. How much more money does she need to buy the handbag?",
      options: ["Rs 150", "Rs 50", "Rs 60", "Rs 90"],
      correctAnswer: "Rs 60",
    },
    {
      question:
        "There are 12 ducks, 18 chickens and 15 cows. How many legs are there altogether?",
      options: ["144", "156", "120", "90"],
      correctAnswer: "120",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Varnika planted some plants in the garden in some rows. If number of plants in a row is same as the number of rows, then which option represents the total number of plants?",
      options: ["9 x 9", "13 x 5", "53 x 1", "3 x 4"],
      correctAnswer: "9 x 9",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Vihan sold 142 apples on Monday. He sold 16 apples less on Tuesday than on Monday. How many apples did he sell altogether on both days?",
      options: ["276", "296", "316", "268"],
      correctAnswer: "268",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Vikram can make a paper boat in 3 minutes. He started making paper boats at 4:30 pm and took a break of 15 minutes. At what time did he finish making 80 paper boats?",
      options: ["8:45 pm", "8:25 pm", "8:15 pm", "9:00 pm"],
      correctAnswer: "8:45 pm",
    },
    {
      question:
        "There are 5 tables in a room and there are 12 chairs around each table. How many chairs are there in the room?",
      options: ["50", "60", "70", "72"],
      correctAnswer: "60",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Tank P contains 40 litres more water than tank Q. Tank R contains thrice as much water as tank Q. If tank R contains 54 litres water, then how much water does tank P can contain?",
      options: ["58 litres", "45 litres", "52 litres", "62 litres"],
      correctAnswer: "58 litres",
    },
    {
      question:
        "5 erasers and 3 sharpners cost Rs 38.  If an erasor costs Rs 4, then how much does a sharpner cost?",
      options: ["Rs 6", "Rs 7", "Rs 4", "Rs 8"],
      correctAnswer: "Rs 6",
    },
    {
      question:
        "For every birthday Vamika's parents put as much money in rupees in a piggy bank as her age in years. How much money will be collected in the piggy bank, when Vamika becomes 5 years old?",
      options: ["Rs 20", "Rs 12", "Rs 15", "Rs 10"],
      correctAnswer: "Rs 15",
    },
    {
      question:
        "A shopkeeper is selling 9 kg sugar for Rs 360. Rajat wants to buy 3 kg sugar. How much does he have to pay?",
      options: ["Rs 150", "Rs 90", "Rs 160", "Rs 120"],
      correctAnswer: "Rs 120",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Identify me. I am a 2D shape. I have 4 sides. All of my sides are equal in length",
      options: ["Rectangle", "Cube", "Triangle", "Square"],
      correctAnswer: "Square",
    }
  ];
  